<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
    <name>Hope (Teasrer)</name>
    <directory>hope (teasrer)</directory>
    <id>3167715373</id>
    <description>WE ARE STILL IN EARLY DEVELOPMENT!

A Funny expansion has entered the basement!
Are you ready for the funniest fuck-up for the game? If you’re stronger than Golem, you might just survive under the giant expansion planned to be updated 24/7, across the board! With help from devs of Devil’s Harvest, Fiend Folio, Revelations, Sacred Dreams, and much more, HOPE, otherwise ported as ANIXBIRTH, is here to bring it on! This mod is planned to pack your game with new experiences, with over…


700+ Monsters! (3 / 700) Kicking ass has never been more fun!
20+ Bosses! (0 / 20) Are you ready for a new challenge?
100+ Items (0 / 100), many custom tailored to experiences in the base game as well as Fiend Folio!
6 (1 / 6) new challenges! You may have been stronger than Golem, but are you stronger than our…
7 (0 / 7) New Characters! Unlock them, and find them hiding in the menu! Can you see where Isaac left them?
Joannes is in the works! Can you rest with a time limit on your hands?
A young swordsman comes this way…
Someone bearing pets comes this way…
Someone unbound to this world comes this way…
A Keeper of thousands comes this way…
A Prince comes this way…
A Song Maiden comes this way…

EVERYTHING UNDER HERE IS PLANNED.
OVER 1,000,000 ROOMS! (100 / 1,000,000) You can’t escape us!
Unlocks! (0 / 700) Over 700, if you decide - or, if you’re lazy, play the game with everything without trying. It’s highly advised you try to unlock our enemies, though.
Compatibility with Fiend Folio’s options pack and Mod Menu Pure! Tailor your experiences to the fullest.
Every OST we could find! Play random, to a soundtrack, or pick exactly what you want!
New rock palettes! Have ones switch out between rooms, or select if there’s a particular sprite sheet you desire.
New pills! Some new ones, some new colors.
Tons and tons of jokes!
We recommend you play us with Fiend Folio, Revelations, Antibirth Monster Pack, Community Remix, THE FUTURE, Boiler, Retribution, Deliverance, Compliance, Devil’s Harvest (rip, don’t) and more! 
We REALLY recommend the Antibirth+++ mod!
UPDATES ONGOING. Suggest what you want in our discord server at Modding of Isaac! We’ll keep our ears - or for some of us, our noses - up high and available!
TONS AND TONS OF ERRORS! Tell us what’s wrong, we’ll try to fix it. 

Find our discord here: https://discord.gg/isaac
</description>
    <version>1.14</version>
    <visibility>Public</visibility>
    <tag id="Lua"/>
    <tag id="Items"/>
    <tag id="Rooms"/>
    <tag id="Enemies"/>
    <tag id="Graphics"/>
    <tag id="Music"/>
</metadata>
